# Sanjok Limbu

A: U 4/172 Stewart Street, Bathurst, 2795 T: 0415 847 834

E: sanlimbz@yahoo.com.au

## Career Objective

Passionate and hard-working graduate seeking an opportunity to work as a Developer. Self-motivated for professional development with 3+ years of experience in customer service, proactive to learn new technologies and certified Bachelor in Information System.

#### **Technical Skills**

Computer Application	Visual Studio, SQL server management studio, Active Directory, Oracle VM Virtual Box, Office 365
Programming	C-Sharp, Java Script
Web Server	Microsoft SQL Server, Azure SQL server
Operating Systems	Windows operating system

## **Employment History**

Team Member Feb 2017 - Present

Coles Supermarket, Bathurst

- Space planning after reviewing huddle report and allocation report from main office
- Maintenance of accurate inventory through attention to daily stock lifecycle using mobile information technology
- Monetary loss is minimized by logging and sending mail for review of potential over stock
- Customer satisfaction of 97% is achieved with proper coordination with team members
- General expenses are slashed to below recommended level of 2% using own judgement on price reduction for quick sale
- Investigate and reporting of continuous improvement opportunities
- Focus in training new team members

## IT Helpdesk May 2019 - Aug 2019

**IIBIT Australia/Federation University** 

- Assisted internal clients and staffs with high quality technical support and computer hardware from either phone, email or face to face communication
- Escalated help desk tickets to higher level support when outside the scope of L1/T1 support providing feedback
- Deployed, supported and maintained ghosted image using Symantec ghost application
- Documented and assigned IDs to new users with related permissions from active directory
- Deployed and troubleshooting windows workstation and presenting enterprise environment
- Liaison with the clients and supplier on procurement, delivery and maintaining contracts while ensuring the continuation and enhancement of services

#### **Personal Projects**

I am a passionate developer and I believe I have adaptability for further training and development to expand my field of work.

https://limbu.azurewebsites.net/

Source code can be viewed here.

https://github.com/SanjokLimbu?tab=repositories

#### Education

Professional Year Oct 2018 - Aug 2018

Performance Education, Sydney

This program is recognised by the Australian Computer Society (ACS) and assists recent graduates in enhancing their employability by developing additional workplace and professional business communication skills.

### **Bachelor's in Business Information Systems**

Dec 2014 - Jun 2018

Australian Institute of Higher Education, Sydney

Key learning areas included: CISCO Networking, Introduction to Programming, Knowledge management, System Analysis and Design, Data mining, Computing, Information Security.

### **Academic Projects**

### **Information System Project**

Jul 2016 - Nov 2016

Australian Institute of Higher Education, Sydney

Objective: To develop and document business requirement and functional specifications for use by developers.

Tools: MS Word, JavaScript, phpMyAdmin, HTML, CSS

Duties: As a group project, I was writing and reviewing system and business requirement and offer solutions for stakeholders after testing.

Outcome: Development of website with all the functional requirement and design.

Result: Received positive Feedback.

Networking Feb 2016 - Jul 2016

Australian Institute of Higher Education, Sydney

Objective: To demonstrate the ability to network computers.

Tools: VMware, Putty, Lan cable, Rack server, Windows 10

Duties: As a group project, I secured the server with multiple security barrier and make it pingable from LAN networked computer as well as remote computer working on windows operating system.

Outcome: All 3 computer and server can successfully ping each other.

Result: Received positive feedback.

#### **Database Management for Business**

Jul 2015 - Nov 2015

Australian Institute of Higher Education, Sydney

Objective: Create a relational database for documentation.

Tools: Xampp, MySQL, PhpMyAdmin

Duties: Created test plans and relational database and identified primary fields and patterns to connect.

Outcome: Successfully created a database available for data entry.

Result: Received positive feedback.

#### Personal Attribute

Leadership skill were demonstrated while leading my team in department when the manager is absent.

Multi-tasking ability was developed while working as a team member as well as looking after the department.

Communication skill was developed while assisting more than 40 customers each day at Coles.

Soft Skills: ITIL V4 Foundation, Interpersonal skills, problem solving, time management.

### References

Referees can be provided upon request.